### Robert Lukas Lundmark

#### About Me

Junior Graphic Designer with 3 years work experience. As a former back-end software engineer, I can effectively communicate product requirements across various technical teams. I am proficient in Web Design and UX Research with a strong interest in Mobile Design.

#### Contact Info

Phone # (302) 723-2066

E-mail elconejo@udel.edu

Portfolio lundmarkdesign.webflow.io/

## Skills & Related Software

Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign

Figma, Sketch

Webflow, Wordpress

Software Engineering

Responsive Design

Wireframes, Mockups

Java, Javascript, HTML

Microsoft Office – Word, Powerpoint, Excel

Computer Graphics & Game Development

### **Work Experience**

#### Freelance UX/Graphic Designer

March 2020 - Present

- Oversee End-to-end design process from requirements gathering to hi-fidelity prototyping
- Conduct customer and industry research
- Construct process deliverables including wireframes, user flows, personas and style tiles

#### **Graphic Designer - Martino Signs, Inc.**

June 2023 - August 2023

- Designing and formatting project bid packages
- Gathering specifications including installation direction, sign artwork, dimensions and location
- Internal projects developing marketing material and stationery

#### Website Manager - First State Martial Arts Academy

July 2016 - Jan 2018

- Designed school branding and mission statement
- Utilized Website Optimization and SEO

## Applications Developer - PJM Interconnections, Accolade, Deloitte Consulting

Jan 2015 - Jun 2016

- Developed and maintained applications using Java, HTML, CSS, SQL and Scala
- Worked alongside UX Team to implement designs

#### **Education**

# Minneapolis College of Art & Design, M.A. in Graphic & Web Design

Jan 2024 - Present

### Delaware College of Art & Design, Web & Graphic Design Certificate

May 2019

#### University of Delaware, B.S. in Computer Science

May 2013